https://www.ntcdistributing.com/privacy-policy/

Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Your privacy is important to us, and we hold our customers and the information they share with us in the highest regard. NTC Distributing is the sole owner of information collected on this website and will not share, sell, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as stated in this policy. Information we may collect include your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, email address, company name, and payment information such as Paypal account, credit card and debit card number. For those who elect to receive our newsletter and promotions or to have access to your account information, we will require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your account.
Information Disclosure to Third Parties
NTC Distributing allows third-party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information when customers visit our website (cookies or a web beacon may be used to collect information). NTC Distributing may use third-party companies to perform functions on behalf. Those functions may include order processing, accounting, shipping calculation, payment processing, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal or email delivery, and data analysis. The third-party companies we employ will not use your personal information for other purposes other than stated in the contracts.
NTC Distributing reserves the right to disclose your personal information as required by law when requested by governmental authorities or to protect our rights.
We use Google Analytics to collect cookie-based anonymous data from our website visitors. Please note that no personally-identifiable information is collected by Google Analytics. Anonymous information collected by Google Analytics is used in aggregate to help us better understand how visitors use our website and improve our product offering and services. You may opt-out of this data collection by clearing your web browser's cookies or by installing the Opt-Out Browser Add-on, which can be found here.
Protection of Personal Information
The security of your personal information is very important to us. The information that you submitted to NTC Distributing may be stored and hosted at a third-party company. Sensitive information will be encrypted and is protected with the best software currently available. The third-party hosting company has an enterprise-level, bank vault security measures that will protect your personal information. The data center of our hosting company employs hacker deterrent security provisioning, three redundant network architectures and hardware firewalls. Your personal information is protected by our hosting company and will be secured.
Retention of Personal Information
For an easier retrieval of existing customers’ personal information, NTC Distributing will retain all customers’ personal information for up to three years. We will sometimes review your personal information to make sure the information is accurate, complete, and up to date. NTC Distributing does not store or retain customers’ financial information such as credit card number, debit card number, bank account numer, Paypal account number, etc. Customers are required to enter payment of method for every order.
Access to Personal Information
NTC Distributing operates in a secured facility with cameras positioned through the facility in conjunction with other alarm systems. Only employees of NTC Distributing with specific job are granted access to personal information.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Connect With Us
NTC Distributing
3041 Olcott St
Santa Clara, CA 95054
Find Uson a Map
All prices are in USD. Copyright © 2020 NTC Distributing. All Rights Reserved.
//
